All...very good burgeoned everybody...
Alecthank you for a waking up...incredibly early in the morning
on-air friday after a fantastic movie how many of you guys...the movie.
Look, at that was it good I couldn't my wife would have called the autonomy
My also at the finishes...of course.
Welcome my name is victor...dot...I
...a program manager in the identity team at microsoft where
...look after developer libraries today I'm going to entertain you
or body you depending...how you react to my accent
...how to take advantage of...active directory from your
native applications which means largely mobile clients.
So, when you target that
...applications you basically have a to possible people?
Want...platform that you want to use so if you...developer and
you're telling us and,...a kind of an obvious choice you
user objective c and if the same goes for android windows
in all the other platforms...you can target however ...not always walking the
...if that's not the yacht platform an effective for a
explaining these finger to known techie is a came out with these analogy
which is basically cuisine national cuisine like if you come from a certain country, you know,
everything about your cuisine a you can appreciate the smallest nuances but the when your
...india and other account tree you can feed adventurers but
...is not always an easy to be open-minded,
for example, a few months ago I was in beijing and street
...trying to let me try this thing and
italians are pretty close-minded when it comes to food and it was kind of I found
...when I...in front of a x called and varies
...objective see thing which on the methods
...to add and deal with the first parameter why
...give you a parameter widely how to put it in there is just medically msing
...as simply I'm not used luckily innovate
modern times there are also other options you can be voice against the language there
...different ways in which you can take advantage
...languages you already know csharp...javascript and are frameworks
that allow you to use your favorite language and target the platform that you want and
that's kind of equivalent of wandering around and?
Even if you are far away from home finding a berea king of course
item go-to berea king even here because I m italian and
...but given that I expected majority the guys out from
the us I tried to craft a metaphor...works for you and...guys are from us.
How many you guys are from china?
All right...I...looks great by
...chide I individuality issue...jellyfish and
...a...soup advanced...
All right now...more serious clearly when we talk about
...upset we are talking about was free big platforms us you have android and you
have all of the flavors of a windows from a classic desktop on windows
salmon to windows start applications to windows phone applications
to now windows universal applications in windows stand I'm going to use is
...you can choose a to leave at the
narrative level you can choose a to operate at the language
level during the starter you'll see details of all these red boxes
for the time being a can just value was at boxes help you to take advantage of
...from your...in fact...even came out with his login event ranks choose a
...stack...hereby.
...memorable.
And, the way which I'm going to structure vis-a-vis as follows first I'm going to
describe which is very high-level
patterned you have to apply when you wanted to take advantage of identity
...negative application these a pattern applies
...across-the-board regardless of the platform...using is
more induce the by the problem and by the protocols that we use then I'm going to explore
what it means to take advantage of a...stocks.
And, I'll go through all the...backwards and then I'll discuss it
how to take advantage of somebody enforce sharper and cordova...javascript
...are suddenly I sound like the pope why do I have an
...mind...adding special effect that it doesn't even public
...events now this session is going to be mostly about the how not...why
I expected that you have been...to many...the offices sessions in which us
...about the they fantastic value of our ecosystem...have been
...body introduction sections...going to re-do...introduction but just for
...you why...doing...the opportunity when you're take advantage of
adjective directory...a really,
really compiling we have...modern...a media on organizations using
this thing if you wanted to integrative office or measure tokens from
actually active directory on the currency that you must use like
...there is no way around it you have a to get it token from ad and this
...even like if you do under wanted to integrate with existing
api is but you want to...just to protect the on assets the...say is that I
...of the mas that powerful thing you can find it on the planet.
Every day we do more than one billion...we have
that many nines...availability so even if you try to do these yourself with your
...is just...difficult to achieve.
So, this is why we're doing it then I will not dot trees again for the
rest representation very good so let's look at...
And,...and we have to dropout.
So, here you have a classic.
Configuration that you can expected to find.
In a and in a scenario where you're
using an active application and specifically what you have it here is...
your...and...resource that you want to access the idea is that the in visa
mobile platforms you have
a resources without on the by the device
...hardware so...storage things like encryption keys things like
...access to your gps positioning...a
...boxing system what applications leave so that you can savory download
evolves up's from a relatively and trusted places like
...upstart and then it was up's can declare what they can do...
sun boxing and farce...that they can do on the what you allow them to do so
you never have direct access to resources...that you have a on windows desktop.
So, what does it take to actually make calls to yadda
...system let me see geeks...
All my stuff.
Okay, normally how does it work your application...access to of that resource
that resources expects it your application to present something to prove that
...boxes...something is typically...access docket so there a number of things
with your application needs to perform one thing
...for example.
Manage to pop out some...experience select the user can
enter that credentials whatever voice might be...might be an access called of
is might be...and password every platform will have a different ways of doing
this so you application must be capable of popping we stuff out.
And, then once you've done vector you need to be able to crafted in message
for the place it from where you are authenticated users and in this
case my sponsors microsoft saw these place would be
...active directory or active directory butter the...the same if you are even walking with
the competitor that's how things would walk and the idea is that the once you
gathered these credentials you have a to be able to perform it
these caller has...to...to some kind of standard typically every of
forty-eight...expect you to authenticate using some authentication
...you want to guess which standard we use in...for the scenario.
It's...need you to be energetic go off thank you
...so much better than me every time...music...
Off and I want...identity...off something like one hundred times a day so that makes
...kind of miserable...anyway...platform visitors
...if everything goes well you get back what we call and access
...okay just an artifact that can be use...for presenting to a resource and get
...and...the next step in here.
...finger...
You grab...
Now normally every good...because the
...satisfaction done of course at realities that I
...because you will not the just make one call and then go away you
would probably keep calling that resource and you will keep
needing that ok so it means about...can mass leave a summer so typically
you wanted to have a savior in some kind of a session and if we...a
...vector things are even more complicated because tokens are short relieved so
...saving that token would not be...you...prompting...for password
in one-hour so but so this...high-level idea of how you would want to
operate and what does that tell us
these tell us vector in order to take advantage of...sauces protected by
...such as active directory your application needs to contain
some logic can be your application or it can be the underlying platform
...somewhere on that device you need the ability of
prompting use crafting of education messages
saving a managing tokens in a session so you need it...thing is which are
used for representing visa logic now this is a high-level now let's go a bit
...and let's look at how you do
...measure active directory adjective directory again I'm not going to do
an introduction but just give an idea it's a...
Every organization can have a projection of...or
...never cloud only directory these directory contains what director is...
contain users application resources and similar and the idea is
vector you axis it using.
Endpoints which represent the internet...the protocols here you
have a collection of endpoints...so it's...I added a sample and...best
...for exhaustive...we do not use them in the mobile
at scenarios mobile scenarios we use only...authorization endpoint
off token endpoint how many of you guys are familiar with...asf operates.
I'm not surprised if you wouldn't you would be still
sleeping somewhat instead of coming to an identity session.
If I will have to wildcat...at talk I would...seeping
In fact admonition not is rhythms and hiring because normally at this time
I'm liking ram phase...for...something nowadays because I'm dreaming.
So, from these access endpoint if we actually we can actually drive of the experience with a
...described earlier but here is an interesting
difference instead of having your logic in your application to random
the experience for gathering credentials what we do is it true ...
libraries so you don't have to do-it-yourself we offer libraries for doing so we actually pop out
...and navigate
...to offer authorization and point this is an endpoint the richer
...in authorization requests randomness
it and authentication experience in your browser so these experience can be as
a simple is a classic use...and can be as complex as user...values out there
...factor off lately my...decided to in make me miserable
handmade...usesecond factor of everywhere I go so
one month ago I was in australia and every time I try to get my made I got a
...from continental us saying please give me european and the client
read hours using was always the same client...didn't have a to deploy...new
...to my machine because of a use the visa trick instead of having
of inactive client produce a ui the pop out the browser and the browser
...ui so the moment which we added
...acceptability these adjust showed up so it's very hand because if
...reason...a huge obtaining?
...employee client...so that's what happens at this point
and that's what happens now another thing which is important to remember about how
do these we've adjective directory
...directory we let never give you a talking unless it
...actors involved in the needs to know the
...that you want to have access to you need to know the...asking for it of course
...needs to know the user otherwise authentication doesn't want any needs to know that
...client...access to was resources
...is kind of ...constrained about for security...I want
...decided what's best so you can imagine vector inside active directory you must have
a little your am a little picture which represents your solution and
that's they only way which you can have a directory to speed things out it's pretty easy
like when you create your app if you use visual studio these happens automatically
for-you otherwise you just go to apart and we see in a second you and a
couple of coordinates and you are provision but you have to do these in advance once
...these and a user successfully authenticate you actually get back from the
token endpoint?
...tokens and here let's say that we are get in for
the green resources so we get the these couple of tokens why do we get a two of them.
One of these tokens...they access token they...the described
area however...access token expires in just one-hour
...comments...here.
after one-hour...are you going to do you can to pop in other dialogue well-off
offers to be great mechanism based on...tokens once I get visa first
access...iso get what is called the refreshed okay when I need a new access
...I can go back to my token endpoint and present my
...token saying hey it's me again...like to have a
new refreshed okay a new access okay and if the user
...still a valid user that...system...sending back...access
...refreshed refresh...so that...leads...this is
...way in which share we give ourselves we opportunity to
...sockets...give you an access documented lasts forever and then...you
...the company or somebody steals your device
...we have a problem...these way the next time at the access
token expires and you come back if...user is no longer valid...I'm sorry...tokens
for so good now in...the we have something that goes even beyond
...we actually have what we call multi resources refreshed...your application needs
...could to exchange and...sharepoint green and...folks.
Instead of having to do it again all the same...dens when I you have to...new
resource here I can actually use the same refreshed ok to ask for
it completely new set the of dawkins font sharepoint.
So, that is point from the user point of view.
A these just happened to transparently in the same way in which...on your
...machine and you're...windows on the internet you just have axis
...knowing what's happening behind-the-scenes this is actually something that happens on
the in adjective directory is not specified the invest standard.
Okay, that's pretty much what they and...theory.
Given the time you still look at remarkably alive...great.
Of course you are doing images as well but that's perfectly fine that's how it was.
Very good saw...theory gun and now let's look at in practice and how to do
these?
...start we've the negative approach save that I
decided vector the best way of experiencing a platform...if you eat
is food so when I am and platform I want to...thing which is negative there?
So, we have a classic ios android and the good all windows as we
know but...in...that we introduce the...new platform which is windows
stand platform which does have...own way of dealing with this.
...here on the to be the...
I wanted to...starting about.
The at...what's on the to worry about making that are network.
So, pretend you didn't see anything that we started from here within cnn.
...you are looking for.
Very good so what happens say is that
...given vector we own windows.
Instead of having to create the libraries and ...
say give you these libraries so that you can use them but in the end we added
...just as much as you on other platforms
windows that we kind of like a can move stuff...like if you want to giga...of
...we gigabyte...we make it...so that's what happened here we decided
that the ability of using these protocols was assign parkland that it
had to be plugged in that platform itself so
...created the no level api...of a system
...anything...part of windows itself and was
...tasks which I described area literally at
...os level instead of putting it in the
up level and how does these walk in windows eight...many of you guys use that
...your machine using
...in a microsoft account the artist formerly known as a live
How many of you guys?
Look, at...okay so you're ready
...fantastic imbedded ness in which you enter your machine with
...credentials and then was credentials are pervasive every time you pop out something
that uses...ideaand,...my marketing is ready to got my hair if I salem
...as...it again...basically ...just walks you
...to worry about any of us aspects in windows stand we added
...visit same level of integration for pleasure active directory you can assign unit to
your device using get in account from yacht adjective
...and then we have api is that allow you to leverage
the same capability from your applications and how
...walk instead of just adding ad alongside with
nsa we actually created a generic plug-in model in which if you
are an identity provider you can just write your plug-in we called
...web account providers and that you can add the
visor providers directly at the system level and then what happens is
...valenza...have access to what we call
...system accounts was...of accounts...you find when you going
to settings menu search for like...
Connected accounts of...current user was out of accounts without all in
...which means that you can actually make when available across-the-board also to other apps
so you can increase...a decrease the number of times which we
...prompt.
And, then we have a new api called the web account manager which is
if the bridge between...capabilities and your application so
...visa api...genetic so you can use
it the same api signature for talking to any of
...supported providers and this thing will make all this stuff of it I described earlier
happen.
that's pretty much...straightforward so here you can imagine that the tokens...you
acquire a saved somewhere at the system level and...together
we've of their capability of prompting the user again these libraries we'll
have a ux to show you...needed to
worry about the creating the ux for gathering credentials we also have
...you access font user selection...that every time you ask
for a talking...system we look for
...system account available and of course...do not just give it to your
...the user needs of to add a chance of saying yep I'm okay we
base up to...as myself with these identity so very is
also a selection experience which allows you to do it's very needs.
The number of api we are in here in a hybrid between the
api is with we adding windows a for...nsa
and the api is that the we have available in our current...
measure active directory libraries when you guys ever use a...yet.
Wow, I'm a proud father here thank you.
Very nice very nice.
Okay, so, here the pattern is very similar...idea is that the
...byacquiring a reference to your provider even if
...provide esau dynamics like a you can add the
decade and identity provider my decided to create a plug-in we have
an api that allow you to select then you...what we call it a web token
request...a...which represents the message that
will be sending and it as adjust some standard parameters and then it
has a mechanism...for adding...specific parameters so, for example,
when you're talking to adjective directory you can talk to many different directories
like every organization has its own whereas when you talk to microsoft account varies a
...the big monolithic single...that you can talk with so in that case you
the needed these ambiguity between one and...
sothese differences are accounted for by crafting the message
...way that adopts to a specific provide...then we have a couple of primitives without of these
...talking a...token silently messing which sounds...zen and
...and basically vases do the same thing the only difference is
...the second one guarantees that if you are doing an action that
can not show any ux this is
...will attempt to get the token without trying anything if it
...just give you an adder instead of popping something out
...get experience and then all these results come back in visa
web token request result you see that these model is actually pretty similar to what we
You can.
I added visas item...people that will download it I know varies a lot of organist and
you can feel free to ignite the message here is as I said ad
...every time you create you want to use leisurely you need to
...drawn your application...and in these point in time which are
bits are still kind of ...quality you kind of a have to do a butter
...still can harry potter move in which if you don say exactly
...of a...the correct...misspell will not walk
but hopefully as we get closer to general availability the sm
...registration operation will be easier retinal long story short
...you need to extract information about your application and you needed to
imbed these information in a special kind of uri and use...when you
...so that when you generate your request
...can actually...talking back to the correcting
...address again I expect these...to be much simpler afterwards
but just want-to make sure...the if you guys at want to play with these afterwards
you download is liza you have...instructions and you don't have to go
through the pain of finding out yourself as I had to do on my jan.
Okay, so.
Time a to switch not the neck yet.
Back to understand okay so my plus with these ...is...
And, now I joke about it later memories.
At least in of...it's...
Ok, so,what you're seeing here is a is vanilla windows
...very simple very straightforward?
And, them so here I'm already using the tokens so let me go
a bit higher just to show you how ie obtain this...
So, as I described earlier.
Here there is a call...they do fatah obtaining my
provider first thing I do is I want a web account provider to which
I can ask it...for and the way which I do...is...I specify.
The base...that I want to use here if I
...and, I say I would specify the url on
and say here instead m specifying the base url of measure ad.
Then once and that I create a web token request.
And, here what I'm passing pretty simply
is vague identifier of my application
...with a added to my.
My...into my...
And,...I...these parameter in which I say it doesn't matter if you're ready
...using the cash I want...audience...about
...I'm actually passing these parameter which I guarantee that...will be a
...that comes out.
And, then I do a couple of things that are ad specific.
Which?
Entailed taking...properties they properties of my web
request and...directory want to talk with in this case I'm using
...developed at ten and...microsoft-dot-com which is might...tenant.
And, then that I...have.
You basically just add the resource but I want to talk we've which is...they graphic
api how many you guys know what is regressive...look at pretty much...everybody else if,
you know, what...easily imagine if this is like...ground, ground...the chide
...dot is l dot the for
...address...distributed multi than system?
And, then at that point they just make my nice call to request
...a seeing bussing these value and then
...results I get back my talking and then later...I make a called
...graph which is very simple...retriever my own.
My unfunded in a system so let's actually run is guy and hop of at the gods of
...internet...agree revise today.
So, here we have...
As soon as a click that parser they system.
Detects with im I call I...talk and possibly...out nbc's...which is being
...from measure ad sightsee today imf.
Now one thing that happens also is that the.
Given...my machine is a...the to a different organization the first-time I
use these user from these other ogg...being the one that
...be getting potentially my provider might ask me to
get some policies on my machine in order for them to give me okay
...up in this case...anyway as you can series obama like hope.
Picture myself in there so,
it was a very simple and very straightforward a just the government...and now
the next time it ad ask for the stoke...in my system and it's very simple.
So, that's how it works on a windows...
And, then of course the
...is that...will walk across all the devices which
...a windows universal address use the universe windows api.
I'd say...probably the only platform meta
unaware of that as a directly in the os
feasibility of doing off all the other negative ops nato's areas of the you
have kind of like higher-level antigen question because ...beginning with was not going to take
session questions saw my fault but the after resign I'll wait until the end yes sir.
It does account manager...account manager is...sorry the question is not the only
...account manager is true on
...account manager and we use it about account manager doesn't really user off it uses
...whatever system you want to use...accounts...also ...as like the
...here I'm a specifically talking about these
...and...providers by the protocol but yes you're absolutely right.
Ok, so, let's say but instead that you are doing a good
...the windows instead of a targeting only windows stand you also
wanted to supporter down level so you might want
to walk on the desktop or you might want to the user they windows a
...on...that one...want to the use of it windows
...that one now...of it...all of these...also
...on windows stand so if you take one of these ox and you run into
...stand it runs it simply it will not integrate
...system level accounts so you might have a bit of a disconnected experience
but it technically if you're ready published your app on the...don't
...it will walk or if you had a desktop utility it will...administer.
So, in order to address was being set we havethese library called the active directory of
indication...now this is a air thank you...
that isn't really a library it's more of like a franchise of libraries
like at it's a it's an artifact which we make available across
a many different platforms which is designed to help you to do exactly
...tasks I described it helps you to be a client
to measure active direct and it's available across all obvious platforms and
...accounting in fact if you have feedback on
...which new platforms you want to see first please let
has no by phone right now is pretty high on the least of course all of these is
open-source if you.
On yadda.
If you go...get tab...measure ad.
Which is it for...a pretty easy to remember address?
If you go in to...address
...would basically find all of our libraries for all our platforms and if
you feel like you are body we can anyone to contribute fantastic features
...the welcome with open arms please do we really like that in fact
these happening all the time like a good portion of...javascript
...media yell at got the community contributions
...pretty good.
The idea is that we try to give you very consistent primitives saw things that
are happy to perform the tasks for their described
...but,...we try to be good citizens of...platforms
...have targeting some.
Earlier I joked about how...to me it sounds to
...to specify...first parameter when you create objective
see methods however again this of a how audit looks to me it's the way which
anti-us operates so we do that so all our libraries behave as we have
supposed to behavior on their own platform but high-level...way which you perform
the tasks and the concepts that you need to manipulate they might change name they might have a different
calling packard but...the same which also applies to
remain saying it becausewe...to manage all these different libraries any each of those would behave
...different way with the probably a commit suicide?
It's not a protocol library now you are insiders so, you know,
now that we use a lot of orf behind-the-scenes but in reality you should not count
on that like we do whatever is necessary to give you a functionality that you want so
...a scenario in which you passes
...and behind-the-scenes we figure out if we have a to use
off...use ws raster we
...fashion...get this summer talking...exchange it for another type of
...all of these happens below the surface and you don't need to worry about in the
...we might completely change what we do as long
as the signature of a...remains the same you should be fine.
And, the zip...a way
...walks we tried to put in the object model all the things that you
think of when you're thinking about your problem even if you don't know anything at all about
...protocol so the first thing iswhat...the user leaving so what is your
...so we have...object which represents the of directory in your
...and that's what we call...context and you create it very easily you just
...they url to your directory why do we ask
for url...about...is...multiple instances...varies
...one that is active public clouding here but when we have other instances,
for example, varies one instance in china which is a
...coupled from these one is an entirely different
instance so if I want to specify that first part of address which maybe...
creative updated because it now is login microsoft online dot com
would be that...the second
...studies in your actual organizations then what actually
...resource meta want to...
you have the client that wants to get the talking of course I
have my users and the tokens...get back so the idea is that I
have a visa acquire focusing is not
with their we use a different name from understand because we don't like you
...want to confuse you is model...matter of a timing this
...came ad layout of than the stuff that came out for windows stand?
And, in these ...we addresses specify what these
...we want in this case with me exchange and they identify
...of a client.
And, the result is represented by these authentication result
...it as information about the user so on so forth.
These syntax
the csharp but...you can expect us to look the same.
Model less java to look the same
...and science...always find enough education context you always find a
...can you will always find enough...result.
Now specifically in ado dot net today the one that is a
...version to invention to we have
a number of things that an interesting we have...features what you
have seen windows stand minus the connection to the operating system because
...as to what goes on down platform and then we have
at the use of a director cameras so if you are and domain join machine
...just take advantage of it and we allow you to give you give us director user
...which you...to do instead...broken and then at
the same package we also have windows runtime components which target they windows
...and windows store for with phone now if you're familiar that we have
the windows runtime components, you know, that was our special kind of libraries
that you can user from any of the languages...you user on windows a
...so even if we wrote of us things in csharp you can use
...from we js you can use them from the cplus-plus.
Those our last...scenarios because we vast majority of people ask
as for csharp but technically if you want to do with you can
do it the other thing is that the voice platforms are sandbox.
So, we know where to...tokens and that keep
...secure...isolated from other apps so that's what we do out-of-the-box we give you
a persistent cash if you up-and-up get
...up next time you open it with token we cb there and you'd be able to use
...and...for ninety days your user will be able to use these we about being
prompted whereas on the desktop we really don't know where you want to
saves stuff so by default we save staff the memory but it's very easy for you
to changer they default cash and use it the on...local these, for example.
And,...just give you a very quick demo.
Let's use these guys so here I'm a doing it pretty much the same stuff
it aidid aryan I have one apt
which retrieves my picture from the directory.
And, the but, we simon doing these...
Maybe within the next couple of...ok so here...classic all the style
Here I have a...which we use very often which I think
it's water demonstrating which is.
...my of indication context is I described earlier so I just
...my...first thing I do...I try to get
...token without popping out and ui so if I have something in my cash
we get lucky and we just get back it okay now if I...manage varies
...very specific one very specific exception that comes out
...may come back here in.
...specific error.
Which says I tried my best
that together is talking about popping anything out aboutthe patient is that?
Then at that point we can catch it and we make the under...the
one in which we know that will pout va the interface and then in that case
you minimize...the popups that a user can have we
also have one flavoring which we do these control yourself but we have not these with
...the fatter to have a visa to lines because it's just easier to debugged
something goes wrong whereas if you just call us and we make
...decision...you have...non diagnostic... what log sir why that...that?
...just hit a five.
... you're ready added document
...any fact here I am and...let me just up-to-date...
So, all very easy and very straightforward and the
called video seen here with apply across...box you can run it on any
version windows not just the desktop.
So, of course one of the questions where they get from my jan...okay
...are now these new api is only the stand and there you have been boarding as
we've ad all for the last couple of years which one you want media...and the answer is
...what have...is best for
your scenario if you are targeting windows universal...on windows stand
...if you use the web account manager of api as we saw earlier than a
you out of the best...direct access to the system
...sauces so I would highly recommend that you use
a web account manager if you needed to run the...also on
...invention windows or...if you actually want to
...use exact same csharp code on ios
...android thenyou might want to use a
...yet also there are things of
...we allow we've ad animosity for legacy...such as,
for example,...and...and...you can't do that with...web account manager so again if,
for example, you needed to do a had less client-but rounds as a
worker all summer then you have a to use a...now the good
news is vector hopefully in a short time will eliminate
...opportunity cost here...national media yellow at the upon waking
up if it realizes that he wakes up and windows stand device instead of
...farming its own calls and using its on cash
...just turn and translate your calls into...web
...web of indicate the web account manager so at that point if you
use idea yell at you...best of both...but we're not there yet so.
Very good okay so
...a negative ios part how many of you guys are ios developers
...five six seven.
Seven yep that's about how many android
...one-two-three-four.
Less windows developers...
Known develops I've seen people that did not to move the
arms at all how are you see awake if you another developer.
...if you have...I'm...a
...us thank you so at very quickly we have a
...a objective see library region objective...is available
...so again pretty standard ios practice
...beanie use the in a many all the way products that you see on
us from microsoft so pretty much all the ios products that you download
on your i-device and if you see something popping out and asking for
...ad credentials they are using
...us is actually shipping...office and
...uses specific features such as
...key chain saw if you...a modern one up you can have all
...tokens because up's from the same publisher can use the same...key
...and given that we use the key chain for saving the tokens you can actually achieve...as
...saw only device across all the apps of your
suit which is pretty nice and it
...scenarios we...part angela.
Android very similar with the difference vector we have like a one
...different ways of installing it you can use marvin you can use gravel you can use
give can you can take zip recur evasive saucer whatever system is a
...workflow we try this apartment and we use
...under the key store for encrypting...your tokens and...we leave them and
...the preference...one that really interesting feature ofunder the library
...it integrates with the account...manager and the pleasure of
indicator up so we have these measure of indicator apple which makes it easier for you to deal we have and,
multi factor off andwe actually...that so if you
edit on board and you...of at...uses a tokens from ad through
...up can broker va...tokens so you can achieve a
ss or across the balked which again is a very nice feature.
...to give all around the languages instead of platforms.
How many you guys ever use it somebody?
...fantastic so for everybody else sony
is a fantastic very
need trick it's like magic theory and which allows you to use a
...to a develop applications and then run those
applications on us and on android of course also windows
...they think that is...magical is...you can open to be...from
...and developed in csharp and we do so because of the ave
the leverage like at runtime...at the know how to run.
Intermediate...intermediate language which is really nice and normally
you structure...a solution we have...it project which contains
it...a...the bulk of your project like your business logic...can
...by creating a portable class library or you can actually
...called and recompile it also when integrated
...other projects and then you ever again csharp,
csharp about platform specific csharp projects which
reference with fart...they take a...all the aspects without
intrinsically different across platforms such as a ux elements
such as a storage and the only things without...platform.
Now how do you actually use ad a
...web we do the kind of a at...I believe is a pretty need to trick.
In the...of asher media yell.
Which supports or visit we have the one-a new get which contains the assemblies
...different flavors we have one part about
class library which contains all of our surface so if you want to make a calls
to our primitives all you need is that part of low-class library and then we have
that platform specific libraries which container ux
...browser specific technology for
saving tokens on a specific area and anything
...which is a platform specific...we do dynamic
...injection necessary vector the idea is that if you
structure your project just like I said earlier when you going to...to you and you say
add the new get the package this is a knows you are doing
...the seattle so it just adds reference to
...specific...then...save that you want to
...than you create...your ios project you create on the you...your...for
ios and then you add the...to your...seattle?
And, it to idea what happens is...the system clearly also brings the
alps selena because it is needed by reference with your using.
But, then also brings of a...specific staff any same goes
...android and for any of the flavors of windows.
In the idea is that the at the last moment you just
passed a reference to a basically pointer to the window of
...electrics with pointer and says harvey's
pointer yep looks like android and bennett grabs
the classes for...showing ux in android and
the injects them in the process so these...allows you to achieve at the highest
...a use so you basically put theof yadda authentication
...here and then you just call-in your high-level library from
the platforms specific barrier which is very neat I really like it.
And, the time to pull out the neck actually before pulling out
...neck let me just show you in visual studio how these looks like.
This is just for giving you an idea in visual studio how that...diagram plays out.
Maybe before tamar.
If you think
of these fink is allowed please make a petition for my boss to buy me a more powerful machine.
And, it's actually partly my fault because they put the far too much stuff.
Mashup.
Get rid of it from the economy is...
Ok, so, now it loaded everything.
Here as you can see here varies they structure that described in
these specific sample we have a very simple up which allows you to...so I have a
part upper-class library which implements these functionality and contains all the calls to
...yet and...face a parameter which says
veer platform specific project when economy
...movies point data to your main window so that will now on which platform I
m and...all of these other platforms...you can see android the desktop
...windows phone windows start?
In all volvos I'm just...back library m just passing the pointer
and nothing else so I'mreallylike I no longer worry about identity at all
it's just taken care of in that aspect.
...more spectacular I'll show you these as
...on the befriend device.
She is...
Every time I lose a ten years of less expectancy thank you.
And, to think...specifically hundred okay what you're seeing here is a
...the same project but the in a
...in-studio summary studio is a development environment
which allows you to open projects strayed from visual studio that
were made that we've...in templates of course you will not be able to
...windows...stuff in here in the same way which you cannot
...maxed stuff on windows but I can run of the next
...here selective user...and just...f five and I'm running
...secularism quality so on the other side.
Is...thing...out a bit?
And, speak out it apparently too big for these screen.
Application here...just
...they...specific path let me say...they want to search for money.
And, then the thing here pops out the.
Pops out the same page rate I get back about as you can see of course
...formatted...because it knows that
...on the neck so it's adapting it according on.
Throughput and.
And, given that these platform.
Doesn't allow me to write these we about you seeing it I
...to do a little black-out here as I write it?
I hope...correctly otherwise I love to do these undermined again.
then I managed to get my token so, basically I'm running a csharp called the directly
ios except we dissimilarity so very nice very straightforward
I could show you exactly the same we've android except that the under the emulator
That...so it doesn't work very
well for edema onstage but there you can
tribes yourself you can just download the samples we are very straightforward.
next we want to talk about...how many of you guys ever use a...
Many...guys know what ease of condom look at
...for everybody else coli is another very need to trick the idea is that
it each provides you we've...special frame.
Where you can render html five applications
...javascript which are actually sitting on your disc so you're
not satin javascript from a set of...it's just
...syntax of language...use it for writing you are
...up and the cordova provides a number of...which
sadder face of the capability of the platform so that despite the fact that you're
...studies frame you can do things like gps you can...things like...anything
...the device allows so we created a plug-in?
That the allows you to actually take advantage of that so very
...invention of a gl of at the walks at...cordova so we have
...a...which represents a javascript facade the
regardless of the platform you out on but then.
Depending on the platform where you install it you end up actually using one of the negative
...so if I don't know us and you run
...you add these plug-in these plug-in will actually bring down also the negative
...so when you call it you're actually using the
...so all the things that I described earlier about
...negative ios you can take advantage of from javascript
...frankly it's amazing to me because you end up writing very little
called and being able to run exactly the same up across multiple
So, here I have a.
Here I am...showing you one of our samples.
Where you just maker?
Pretty much the same...meta was this running...acquittal can...if he doesn't walk
acquire token fool and it...saw javascript is exactly the same
...across-the-board it's just these file...js file
in the a varies a little html file of...online application needs is badly two
hundred lines of code and it's all based on common line.
So, I can just say current java emulate ios.
Pops out emulator.
Loads the cordova frame.
...loads html file operator described loads
...javascript behind it and it gets me and, this
...my local a ux...the same
...described for examined butter for the spot.
show you...is actually using the lock-out...as you can cvs what the right away because
...ready...a token cashed like a use the my inactive eighty
...us for another up so here I read...the my
token cashed so if you are if javascript is your finger cordova is pretty much
...way to go for doing this stuff.
Okay, so, we did event.
For once I manager than...not to have...skip and his lights
...all of them and I still twenty second nineteen eighteen saw as
I promise...if you want to use educate
directory you are free to choose to go on negative all the way
or you can use any of the
multi target platform stocks that are available on the market whatever you choose where
...back we make it very easy for you to take advantage of it.
Now...take some questions but not a...because unfortunately
somebody in the organization really...me and they put another session
...afterwards so...to do a couple of adjustments so...
So, the question user is there any chance of.
Adopting the level of education depending on the type of client.
And, outside of premium and I think that at this point in time
in a tree we are walking on a having a granular accesses
...we...policies with are based on the your device so run and then
...wpf of asses at web it'd be something the effect of a allow you to do
certain things only if you're showing...talking about...being a
obtained from a trusted device but that I actually cannot
value if that will require premium or if it will be available to everybody I can follow-up.
...yes sir.
Samoa.
...question user is it possible to plug...a...multi-band multi
...factor...immeasurably...easier?
As long as a you do...on premises that's a
...actually does not run your own code...each wheeler
...your lock-out afs if you are projecting your
directly from your own premises the latest...supportive
...has extensibility points which allow you to plug-in...a custom of.
...factor so at this point you can leverage about the and that the
mechanism for shipping, you know.
I can look it up and give that to you offline.
All right so yes, sir.
The question is it possible to user tokens where they get from...to secure my own api and the
answer is absolutely yes and in fact if you...to our?
If you go to our samples page.
Samples.
And, use...for any it is reach thank you.
And, you search...now you're
...private...represented...gradients sari.
...sej for web api.
Why is it not filtering okay?
...ones here let's say...api typically
...project that you find a solution which is a...whether
the any chose you how to use ...midwest for protecting
your own api format validating with organic comes in and
...extracted the identity...of...that you have it available from your own
...whether api in...session...one hour and a half I'm going to touch on that as well.
All right yes sir.
So, the question is how would you deal with multiply these...known...
Whiny use...yell the assumption is that you will use...active directory
beat afs or...ad...what we assume
like if you want to use a different providers you have to deal with that on...
libraries however if you are using multiple measure...
than that it's very easy every time you needed to talk to a different...you
...different of education context...a different for...so if you are working with
conversion fabric and you create...of education context busing login microsoft online
...calms...microsoft-dot-com and the other one is a
gains condos and then when you ask...using a one context of
other context you'll get different ones and there you can actually...a use the same
...cash so...needed to maintain a different starts
...cache will know how to keep...being separated?
We do...there again...add a follow-up is we have to look at the user and see
what goes we added mechanisms...you can also
...context bypassing a speciality keywords instead
on a tenant instead of saying ...or fabric and you say common and...it
...directory vector you want to the user to...side
...these ...actual directed at runtime and once
...types seenthe user any of a...tab this being a goes
the back-end looks at the corresponding domain finds out if it's only
...if a resource and afs varies
...what these garrison...so we do all of that and once you get back
...token we extractor from
...response of information and we update your context so that if you creative
...context saying the car common but then after watts you inspected you see that
...it would be contours because once we
...we know vector it's no longer ambiguous you wanted to be condos.
I would...just...and...we level to we'll have to run because I think that the
vilnius somebody we needed to set the stuff up.
...yelled...vitaly so how you sort of like.
Looking for solutions...narrow versus this type of like html.
So, the question is on.
Differences between...a...windows...different scenarios so
if you opportunity to counter accession your cvs mark...the idea is
...windows at a foundation really the app plays a different all windows
...foundation was designed to protect resources whereas in this
case you out on the other side on the equation instead of us sitting in front of
resource and making...only of indicated caustic place you-are-there
...a talk and that you need to send in order to satisfy
...watch-dog and,
we no longer user windows...for what we see supported but we now have more modern lash
...perform the same task
...idea here is...the when you use a aga yell normally...not calling a web
...but according a web api so they protocol that you use...different
negative web...and...you play with cookies whereas when you...api
...have a context for cookies you just get tokens and you send them
...so normally you would not protected...api using windows at any foundation
...what is possible it's a bit of a...but it's possible you the study use
these new modern a libraries...all...again if you have an opportunity
...happy to show that afterwards great...go ahead?
Correct.
You have...when you create your in a entry with describes your
application image directory you have to declare a what out of their resources
...will ask a access for and then it's still up to the user to
...or deny a consented forgetting was resources but we need to
...information becausewhen you ask for a talking...your customa
custom api lack of a gentleman described you...to be able to say voice-over things with any
to have access or...it them getting...to you are web
...api in itself a needs to access to exchange sharepoint and...you don't want to...user
...too many problems so if you specify all of that stuff in advance once the
ad shows you the consent page it can aggregate all the things that you need so that
...just one place and which it says okay
but great thanks-again and now I just turn everything...